Guide to the Inge Morath Photographs and Papers GEN MSS 996
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographs, 1896-2001; 1; 707430; 136.99 Linear Feet (550 boxes)
  - Contact Sheets, 708395
    - Personal Set, 708837
      - 1985-08. Mara Thorpe, Judge of the Family Court of the State of New York, Manhattan, New York City (Roll 1), 708956 (Box 89)
      - 1985-09. Julian Schnabel, artist and filmmaker, with Arthur Miller, Long Island, New York (Roll 1), 708955 (Box 89)
      - 1985-10. No story at this number (No rolls recorded), 708954 (Box 89)
      - 1985-11. Mayra Langdon, actress and producer (Rolls 1-3), 708953 (Box 89)
        Includes Mara Thorpe, Judge of the Family Court of the State of New York, Manhattan, New York City, and Rebecca Miller
      - 1985-12. Maeve Slavin, journalist and author (Roll 1), 708952 (Box 89)
      - 1985-13. Arthur Miller photographed for the London Times (Roll 1), 708951 (Box 89)
      - 1985-14. Trip with group of writers to Lithuania and Moscow, Soviet Union (Rolls 1-26), 708950 (Box 90)
        Includes Bella Akhmadulina, Chyngyz Aitmatov, Charles Fuller, William Gaddis, William H. Gass, Allen Ginsberg, Arthur Miller, Harrison E. Salisbury, and Yevgeny Yevtushenko
      - 1986-01. Family life and personal (Rolls 1-10), 708949 (Box 90)
        Includes production of Pirosmani, Prisomani, probably by the Vilnius Youth Theatre, Lithuania; meeting with Chinese authors, including Zhang Jie; annual reception of the American Academy of Arts and Letters, which includes attendees novelist Ralph Ellison, playwright Edward Franklin Albee, novelist William Styron, and museum director Monroe Wheeler; images of poet Gregory Corso, poet Alan Ginsberg, Arthur Miller, and landscape architect and sculptor Isamu Noguchi; stills from A Truth About Paradise, a film by Rebecca Miller, which include novelist Barbara Browning
      - 1986-02. Allen Ginsberg, poet, visiting Arthur Miller and Inge Morath in Roxbury, Connecticut (No rolls recorded), 708948 (Box 90)
        Includes poet Andrei Voznesensky and Inge Feltrinelli, photographer and publisher
      - 1986-03. PEN International Meeting in New York (Rolls 1-38), 708947 (Box 90)
        Includes Saul Bellow, author; Breyten Breytenbach, author and painter; E. L. Doctorow, author; Hans Magnus Enzensberger, author and poet; Günter Grass, novelist, poet, playwright, illustrator, and sculptor; Nadine Gordimer, author; Mario Vargas Llosa, author; Norman Mailer, author, playwright, film maker, and actor; Wang Meng, author; Heiner Müller, dramatist, poet, author, and director; Amos Oz, author; Peter Schneider, novelist; United States Secretary of State George P. Shultz; John Updike, author, poet, and critic; and Kurt Vonnegut, author
      - 1986-04. Vienna: Lusthaus, a theatrical piece created and directed by Martha Clarke, rehearsals at St. Clement's Episcopal Church, New York City (Rolls 1-3), 708946 (Box 90)
      - 1986-05. Ilse Getz, painter and collage artist, in Newtown, Connecticut (Rolls 1-2), 708945 (Box 90)
      - 1986-06. Homeless of New York (Rolls 1-3), 708944 (Box 90)
        Includes Third Avenue Men's Shelter, as well as dance/movement and creative arts therapist Judith Ginzberg
      - 1986-07. Arthur Miller and Mark Lamos, director, producer and actor (No rolls recorded, color photographs), 708943 (Box 90)
      - 1986-08. Madrid, Spain (Rolls 1-20), 708942 (Box 90)
        Includes Luis Escobar Kirkpatrick, actor, director and playwright; Núria Espert, actress and director; Luis Gordillo, painter; and Darío Villalba, painter and photographer
      - 1986-09. Barcelona, Spain (Rolls 1-19), 708941 (Box 91)
        Includes Park Güell, as well as sites at Cadaqués and Costa Brava. Also includes a visit with the children of Lola Ruiz de Vilató, sister of Pablo Picasso, who Morath photographed in 1954, including Lolita Vilató Ruiz and Pablo Vilató Rui
      - 1986-10. Home of Louis-Ferdinand Céline, writer, and his wife, Lucette Almanzor, in Meudon, France (Rolls 1-2), 708940 (Box 91)
      - 1986-11. Rebecca Miller (No rolls recorded), 708939 (Box 91)
      - 1986-12. Harold Pinter, playwright, screenwriter, director and actor, photographed for the London Sunday Times (Rolls 1-3), 708938 (Box 91)
      - 1986-13. Issyk Kul Culture Forum, at Lake Issyk Kul, Kyrgyzstan, Soviet Union (Rolls 1-15), 708937 (Box 91)
      - 1986-14. The Archbishop's Ceiling, by Arthur Miller, rehearsals at the Barbican Theatre, London, England (No rolls recorded), 708936 (Box 91)
      - 1986-15. St. Louis, Missouri, and William H. Gass, novelist, short-story writer, essayist, critic, and philosophy professor (No rolls recorded), 708935 (Box 91)
      - 1987-01. Family life (Roll 1), 708934 (Box 91)
        Includes Louise Bourgeois, sculptor; Fazil Iskander, author; James Lancel McElhinney, painter; Juna Moritz, author and translator; and Andy Warhol, artist
      - 1987-02. Danger: Memory!, a production consisting of two one-act plays, I Can't Remember Anything, and Clara, by Arthur Miller at the Lincoln Center Theater, New York City (No rolls recorded), 708933 (Box 91)
      - 1987-03. Rebecca Miller with "Mycenaean jukebox" (No rolls recorded), 708932 (Box 91)
      - 1987-04. Arthur Miller during production of Danger: Memory!, consisting of plays I Can't Remember Anything and Clara, at the Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, New York City (Rolls 1-28), 708931 (Box 91)
        Includes Arthur Miller visiting Hotel Chelsea in New York City with its owner Stanley Bard; Miller with poet Andrei Voznesensky at a reading by the latter at The Public Theater in New York City; Allen Ginsberg, poet; and Rebecca Miller in her Brooklyn studio
      - 1987-05. Television program Good Morning America interview with Inge Morath for exhibition and publication, Portraits (New York: Aperture, 1986) (Rolls 1-3), 708930 (Box 91)
        Includes pianist Israela Margalit and journalist Judith Miller
      - 1987-06. Forum for a Nuclear-free World and the Survival of Mankind, in Moscow, Soviet Union (Rolls 1-21), 708929 (Box 91)
        Includes General Secretary Mikhail Gorbachev, and his wife Raisa Gorbachova; as well as Bella Akhmadulina, poet; probably Eugenia "Juna" Davitashvili, poet and clairvoyant; Graham Greene, author; Elem Klimov, film director; probably Asaf Messerer, ballet dancer and teacher; Bulat Okudzhava, poet, musician, and author; Yoko Ono, multimedia artist, singer, and activist; Maya Plisetskaya, ballet dancer; Andrei Sakharov, nuclear physicist, dissident and human rights activist; Rodion Shchedrin, composer and pianist; Lev Shilov, sound archivist; ballet dancer Vladimir Vasiliev, and his wife, ballet dancer Ekaterina Maximova; probably Venedikt Yerofeyev, author; Galina Volchek, actress; Andrei Voznesensky, poet; and Yevgeniy Yevtushenko, poet
      - 1987-07. Vladimir and Suzdal, Soviet Union, and Armenia (Rolls 1-6), 708928 (Box 91)
      - 1987-08. Janusz Głowacki, author and screenwriter, and Dianne Wiest, actress (Rolls 1-34), 708927 (Box 91)
        Includes The Cherry Orchard, by Anton Chekhov, directed by Peter Brook, at the Majestic Theatre, Brooklyn Academy of Music, New York City, which included Rebecca Miller as Anya, as well as images of Gregory Mosher, director and producer
        Also includes poet Bella Akhmadulina, and her husband, artist Boris Messerer, visiting with Thomas P. Whitney, translator and diplomat, and Arthur Miller
      - 1987-09. No story at this number (No rolls recorded), 708926 (Box 91)
      - 1987-10. England with Arthur Miller (Rolls 1-4), 708925 (Box 91)
        Includes production of View from the Bridge, written by Arthur Miller, produced by the National Theatre of Great Britain at the Cottesloe Theatre, directed by Alan Ayckbourn, and starring actor Michael Gambon
        Also includes playwrights Harold Pinter, Simon Gray, and Arthur Miller at Pinter's home, as well as the wife of Pinter; author Antonia Frazer with Rebecca Miller; and Arthur Miller with director and producer Nick Hamm
      - 1987-11. Ronda, Spain, photographed for Condé Nast Traveller magazine (Rolls 1-5), 708924 (Box 91)
      - 1987-12. Seville Fair (Feria de abril de Sevilla), Spain, photographed for Condé Nast Traveller magazine (Rolls 1-3, includes color photographs), 708923 (Box 91)
      - 1987-13. A group of Russian directors and actors visiting Roxbury, Connecticut (Roll 1), 708922 (Box 91)
        Includes director Eimuntas Nekrošius and actress Anastasiya Vertinskaya
      - 1987-14. No story at this number (No rolls recorded), 708921 (Box 91)
      - 1987-15. Copies of photographs and portraits for illustrations for Arthur Miller, Timebends: A Life (New York: Grove Press, 1987) (Rolls 1-2), 708920 (Box 91)
      - 1987-16. Bel Kaufman, author, teacher, and granddaughter of Sholem Aleichem, in Manhattan (Rolls 1-2), 708919 (Box 91)
      - 1987-17. Fishing off in the Hudson River near Nyack, New York (Roll 1, includes color photographs), 708918 (Box 92)
      - 1987-18. Gilles Peress and Janice Hart and a Magnum Photos meeting (Roll 1, includes color photographs), 708917 (Box 92)
        Includes Adolf Galland, a German Luftwaffe general and flying ace, at the Experimental Aircraft Association annual meeting in Oshkosh, Wisconsin
      - 1987-19. Bob Kuhn, wildlife artist, in Roxbury, Connecticut (Roll 1), 708916 (Box 92)
      - 1987-20. Rebecca Miller filming and directing her Crane movie in Brooklyn, New York City (Rolls 1-2), 708915 (Box 92)
      - 1987-21. Bicentennial celebration of the United States Constitution on the Southbury Green, Connecticut (Rolls 1-2), 708914 (Box 92)
        Includes sculptor Christopher Hewat, with wooden constructions in his studio in Salisbury, Connecticut
      - 1987-22. Miscellaneous (Rolls 1-4), 708913 (Box 92)
        Includes Arthur Miller and Rebecca Miller, as well as translator Lobsang P. Lhalungpa and his wife, Gisela Minke
        Images also depict poet Honor Moore, as well as jewelry in her collection made by Alexander Calder for the Musée des Arts Décoratifs in Paris, France
      - 1987-23. No story at this number (No rolls recorded), 708912 (Box 92)
      - 1987-24. Arthur Miller and Edward Albee, playwright, in Albee's loft in Soho, New York City (Roll 1), 708911 (Box 92)
      - 1987-25. Rebecca Miller in a studio on Broome Street in New York City, photographed for Vogue magazine (Rolls 1-3), 708910 (Box 92)
      - 1987-26. Issyk Kul Culture Forum in Wengen, Switzerland, hosted by Peter Ustinov (Rolls 1-5), 708909 (Box 92)
        Includes Ilse Aichinger, author; Chyngyz Aitmatov, author; Friedrich Dürrenmatt, author and dramatist, and his wife, Charlotte Kerr, director, producer, actress, and writer; Alexander King, scientist and co-founder of the Club of Rome; Giuseppe Santomaso, painter; Roger Taillibert, architect; and Peter Ustinov, and his wife, Helene du Lau d'Allemans.
        Also includes Miller and Morath visiting the home of Taillibert and Kerr in Neuchâtel, Switzerland, as well as Arthur Miller reading from Timebends: A Life (New York: Grove Press, 1987) at the Goethe University Frankfurt, Germany
      - 1987-27. Berlin, West Germany (Rolls 1-4), 708908 (Box 92)
        Includes author Lev Kopelev, Arthur Miller, and photographer Helmut Newton
      - 1987-28. Promoting Arthur Miller, Timebends: A Life (New York: Grove Press, 1987) in London and Manchester, England, and in Paris, France (Rolls 1-26), 708907 (Box 92)
        Includes actors Michael Billington and Michael Gambon, as well as Harold Pinter, playwright, screenwriter, director and actor
      - 1987-29. Promoting Arthur Miller, Timebends: A Life (New York: Grove Press, 1987) in Washington, D.C.; Los Angeles and San Francisco, California, and Boston, Massachusetts (Rolls 1-7), 708906 (Box 92)
      - 1987-30. Soledad Puértolas Villanueva, author, visiting the Queen Sofía Spanish Institute in New York City with a group of Spanish authors (Roll 1), 708905 (Box 92)
      - 1988-01. Life in Roxbury, Connecticut (Rolls 1-25), 708904 (Box 92)
        Includes Zoya Boguslavskaya, writer; René Burri, photographer; Philip Grausman, sculptor; Francine du Plessix Gray, author and critic; A. R. "Pete" Gurney, playwright and novelist, and his wife Molly, at the wedding of their daughter; Eric Hobsbawm, historian; Jacques Kaplan, furrier and art gallery owner; Sean Landers, artist; James Lancel McElhinney, painter; Sean Landers, artist; Meda Mládková, art collector; Rebecca Miller; Arthur Miller; Honor Moore, poet and playwright; Karel Reisz, filmmaker; Volker Schlöndorff, filmmaker; Oleg Tselkov, artist at the Eduard Nakhamkin Fine Arts gallery, New York City; Margarethe von Trotta, film director; and Debra Winger, actress, with her son, Noah Hutton
        Also includes copy photographs of Arthur Miller's parents, Augusta Barnett Miller and Isidore Miller, with Marilyn Monroe
      - 1988-02. Vivien H. Lu, senior lector in Chinese at Yale University, portraits for New Haven Art Space (Rolls 1-3), 708903 (Box 92)
      - 1988-03. No story at this number (No rolls recorded), 708902 (Box 92)
      - 1988-04. Backstage women's dressing room at a performance of The Cherry Orchard, by Anton Chekhov, directed by Peter Brook, at the Majestic Theatre, Brooklyn Academy of Music, New York City (Rolls 1-2), 708901 (Box 92)
        Includes actresses Ludmila Bokievsky, Linda Hunt, Kate Mailer, Rebecca Miller, Natasha Parry, and Stephanie Roth
      - 1988-05. Louis Stanton Auchincloss, lawyer, novelist, historian, and essayist (Rolls 1-2), 708900 (Box 92)
      - 1988-06. Holy Week in Seville, Spain, as well as views of Madrid (Rolls 1-25), 708899 (Box 92)
      - 1988-07. Inge Morath Retrospective at the Union of Photojournalists in Moscow, Soviet Union (Rolls 1-14), 708898 (Box 93)
        Includes Nika Kosenkova, actress and director; Svetlana Makurenkova, translator; Yevgeny Yevtushenko, and his wife, Maria Novikova; and Slava Zaitsev, fashion designer, as well as the gravesite of Vladimir Vysotsky, singer-songwriter, poet, and actor, at the Vagankovskoye Cemetery in Moscow; and views of Zagorsk (Sergiyev Posad)
      - 1988-08. Promoting Arthur Miller, Timebends: A Life (New York: Grove Press, 1987) in Paris, France (Rolls 1-7), 708897 (Box 93)
        Includes Bernard Pivot, journalist; François Perrier, psychoanalyst; and editors from Editions Grasset et Fasquelle; as well as Umberto Eco, OMRI is an Italian semiotician and Milan, Italy
      - 1988-09. Honor Moore, poet, portrait for her Memoir: Poems (Goshen, Connecticut: Chicory Blue Press, 1988) (Rolls 1-3), 708896 (Box 93)
        Includes Rebecca Miller filming her friend, novelist Barbara Browning, and Begonia Medina, author
      - 1988-10. Tama Janowitz, novelist and a short story writer, in Manhattan, New York City (Roll 1), 708895 (Box 93)
      - 1988-11. Ed McBain, also known as Evan Hunter, author and screenwriter, in Connecticut (Roll 1), 708894 (Box 93)
      - 1988-12. Jay McInerney, writer and food critic, in New York City (Roll 1), 708893 (Box 93)
      - 1988-13. Volker Schlöndorff and Margarethe von Trotta, filmmakers, in Roxbury, Connecticut (Rolls 1-2), 708892 (Box 93)
        Includes Rebecca Miller with the family dog, Lola
      - 1988-14. Women coal miners at the Bailey Mine, Pennsylvania, photographed for Marie Claire magazine in the United Kingdom (Rolls 1-11), 708891 (Box 93)
      - 1988-15. Inge Morath Retrospective at the Sala del Canal Museum in Madrid, Sala del Canal (Rolls 1-5), 708890 (Box 93)
        Includes Juana de Aizpuru, art gallery owner and collector; probably Luis Escobar Kirkpatrick, actor; Arthur Miller; and Beatriz de Moura, editor
      - 1988-16. Arthur Miller and Karel Reisz, filmmaker, looking at locations in Norwich, Connecticut for movie Everybody Wins (Rolls 1-2), 708889 (Box 93)
      - 1988-17. Francine du Plessix Gray, author, and Zoya Boguslavskaya, writer and wife of Andrei Voznesensky (Rolls 1-2), 708888 (Box 93)
        Note by Morath, "don't like take"
      - 1988-18. Catherine Chermayeff, Director of Special Projects, Magnum Photos, and her husband, Jonathan David (Rolls 1-2), 708887 (Box 93)
      - 1989-01. Miller family life (Rolls 1-12), 708886 (Box 93)
        Includes Aharon Appelfeld, novelist; Batuz, artist, philosopher and cultural activist; Joyce Chopra, director and writer; Walter Cronkite, journalist; Diane von Fürstenberg, fashion designer; Eda Kriseova, author; Begonia Medina, author; Arthur Miller; and Debra Winger, actress, with her son, Noah Hutton
        Also includes Rebecca Miller leaving for Austria for the filming as the lead actress in "Georg Elser - Einer aus Deutschland," also known as "Seven Minutes," directed by Klaus Maria Brandauer, as well as images from a meeting of Magnum photographers
      - 1989-02. Cairo and Luxor, Egypt (Rolls 1-11), 708885 (Box 93)
        Includes Naguib Mahfouz, author
      - 1989-03. Israela Margalit, pianist, bringing music of Mozart to group of Harlem schoolchildren, probably at the Harlem School of the Arts (Rolls 1-2), 708884 (Box 93)
      - 1989-04. Norwich, England (Rolls 1-5), 708883 (Box 93)
        Includes founding of the Arthur Miller Centre for American Studies at the University of East Anglia, Norwich, as well as an Inge Morath exhibition, Portraits at the Norwich Cathedral, Norwich.
        Also includes Malcolm Bradbury, writer, and his wife, Elizabeth Salt Bradbury, a radio dramatist; Bill Gallagher, writer; Peter M. Mayer, publisher; Alan Plater, playwright and screenwriter; David Thacker, theatre director; and Arnold Wesker, playwright
      - 1989-10. Arthur Miller with a new hat (Roll 1), 708882 (Box 93)
        Includes painter Natalia Nesterova
      - 1989-11. Moscow and Tver (Kalinin) in the Soviet Union, as well as Vilnius and Kaunus in Lithuania (Rolls 1-34), 708881 (Box 94)
        Includes the Stanislavsky House Museum in Moscow, as well as members of Sąjūdis, a political organization for Lithuanian independence, Lithuanian artists, and actors in the State Youth Theatre of Lithuania
      - 1989-12. The Cherry Orchard, by Anton Chekhov, produced by Peter Brook at the Taganka Theater in Moscow, Soviet Union (Rolls 1-4), 708880 (Box 94)
      - 1989-13. Everybody Wins, film with a screenplay by Arthur Miller and directed by Karel Reisz (Rolls 1-6), 708879 (Box 94)
        Includes cast members Nick Nolte, Jack Warden, and Debra Winger
      - 1989-14. Creation of Endangered Species, ballet by Martha Clarke, choreographer and director, in South Carolina and Connecticut with dancers and animals (Rolls 1-22), 708878 (Box 94)
      - 1989-15. Francine du Plessix Gray, author, portrait for her for Soviet Women: Walking the Tightrope (New York: Doubleday, 1990) (Rolls 1-2), 708877 (Box 94)
      - 1989-16. Rebecca Miller trying out shots for a film, The Awakening (Rolls 1-2), 708876 (Box 94)
        Includes novelist Barbara Browning
      - 1989-17. Soviet Union with Progress Publishers (Rolls 1-43, includes color images), 708875 (Box 94)
        Includes views of Koktebel, Leningrad (Saint Petersburg), Moscow, Pereslavl-Zalessky, Rostov, Simferopol, Yalta, and Yaroslavl
      - 1989-18. Fall of the Berlin Wall, Germany (Rolls 1-12, includes color photographs), 708874 (Box 94)
      - 1989-19. Arthur Miller (Roll 1), 708873 (Box 94)
      - 1989-20. Barbara Ungeheuer, journalist, in Roxbury, Connecticut (Rolls 1-2), 708872 (Box 94)
      - 1990-01. Family life in Roxbury, Connecticut and New York with Arthur Miller and Rebecca Miller (Rolls 1-23?), 708871 (Box 95)
        Includes A. R. "Pete" Gurney, playwright and novelist; Alfred Kazin,writer and literary critic; and Ute Eskildsen, curator
      - 1990-02. London, England (Rolls 1-3), 708870 (Box 95)
        Includes rehearsals of The Price, by Arthur Miller, directed by David Thacker, at the Young Vic Theatre, London, England, as well as portraits of authors Antonia Fraser and Doris Lessing
        Also includes the Department of Greece and Rome at the British Museum
      - 1990-03. Berlin, Germany (Rolls 1-3), 708869 (Box 95)
        Includes views of the Plötzensee Memorial and Berlin Wall
      - 1990-04. Moscow and Peredelkino, Soviet Union, for the Boris Pasternak centennial (Rolls 1-3), 708868 (Box 95)
        Includes interiors of the Pasternak House Museum in Peredelkino, and the dacha poet Yevgeny Yevtushenko, and his wife, Maria Novikova, as well as images of author Chyngyz Aitmatov
      - 1990-05. Earth Day on Avenue of the Americas and in Central Park, New York City (Rolls 1-3), 708867 (Box 95)
      - 1990-06. Arthur Miller in Roxbury, Connecticut, photographed for Süddeutsche Zeitung (Rolls 1-3), 708866 (Box 95)
      - 1990-07. Michael Riesman, composer, conductor, keyboardist, and record producer, in New York City (No rolls recorded, color photographs), 708865 (Box 95)
      - 1990-08. Ernst Neizvestny, sculptor, painter, graphic artist, including his studio in Manhattan, New York City (Roll 1), 708864 (Box 95)
      - 1990-09. Florence short film by Rebecca Miller, including cast members Marsha Gay Harden and Robert Younger (No rolls recorded), 708863 (Box 95)
      - 1990-10. Endangered Species, ballet by Martha Clarke, choreographer and director, rehearsals at the Brooklyn Academy of Music, New York City (No rolls recorded), 708862 (Box 95)
      - 1990-11. Arthur Miller 75th birthday celebration at the at the Vivian Beaumont Theater, Lincoln Center, New York City (No rolls recorded), 708861 (Box 95)
      - 1990-12. Andrei Voznesensky, poet and writer, and Allen Ginsberg, poet (No rolls recorded), 708860 (Box 95)
      - 1990-13. Evgeny Pasternak, the literary critic and son of author Boris Pasternak (Rolls 1-2), 708859 (Box 95)
        Includes Anatoly Rybakov, author
      - 1990-14. Capetown and Johannesburg in South Africa, and Nelson Mandela (No rolls recorded), 708858 (Box 95)
      - 1991-01. Family life in Roxbury, Connecticut with Arthur Miller and Rebecca Miller (Rolls 1-27), 708857 (Box 95)
        Includes images of Louise Bourgeois, sculptor, at her studio in Brooklyn, New York City, and her assistant Jerry Gorovoy and editor Peter Blum
        Also includes Martha Clarke, choreographer and director, rehearsing with dancer Félix Blaska; Sam Cohn, talent agent at International Creative Management; John Guare, playwright; Pavel Lungin, filmmaker; John Malkovich, actor, director, and producer, and his partner Nicoletta Peyran, with their daughter Amandine Malkovich; Honor Moore, poet and playwright; Mathilde Wiesler Morath, mother of Inge Morath; John Tillinger, director and actor; Arnold Weinstein, poet and playwright; and Yevgeny Yevtushenko, and his wife, Maria Novikova
        Additionally includes Newport, Rhode Island during the filming of "Wind," which included Rebecca Miller in the role of Abigail Weld
      - 1991-02. Berlin, Germany, and meeting of Société Imaginaire (Rolls 1-12), 708856 (Box 96)
        Includes Marcos Aguinis, author; Napoleón Baccino Ponce de León, novelist; Jochen Boberg, historian and curator; Jacek Bocheński, poet and author; Nicolas Cocarfo, poet and author; Timothy J. Keating, translator; Ivan Klíma, novelist and playwright; Álvaro Mutis, poet and author; Juan Sánchez Peláez, poet; Mark Strand, poet; and Leszek Szaruga, poet and author
        Also includes views of Potsdam, including Sanssouci, the former summer palace of Frederick the Great, King of Prussia
      - 1991-03. Salzburg, Austria (Rolls 1-30), 708855 (Box 96)
        Includes photographs for book, Thomas Joshua Cooper and Harald Waitzbauer, Salzburg, an Artist's View (Salzburg: Edition Fotohof im Otto Müller Verlag, 1991)
      - 1991-04. Mary Frank, sculptor, in her studio in Lake Hill, New York (Rolls 1-3), 708854 (Box 96)
      - 1991-05 to 1991-10, 708853 (Box 96)
      - 1991-11 to 1991-15, 1992-01 to 1992-08, 708852 (Box 97)